Hey. Do you wanna team up?
-Nah. Thanks.
-Wha...
[ELYMAS] A Fang of
Smoldering Insanity skill book.
If I had one in my possession,
I'd be able
to unlock an entire skill tree.
They're extremely rare,
so I won't find one right away,
but looking for one is free.
Oath of the Heavy Armor.
And Fang of Smoldering Insanity.
These are two skill trees
that work together
to complete the Heavy Knight.
And when that happens,
the Heavy Knight is no longer
a defense specialist,
but referring to it
as an offense specialist
isn't right either.
At that point,
it becomes a human weapon.
If I want to move forward
and unlock my true potential,
Fang of Smoldering Insanity
is vital.
[indistinct chatter]
[♪ opening theme song playing]
[♪ bright music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
Whoa, she's so cute!
[sighs] Who am I kidding?
Hmm.
-Now, don't you waste it.
-Oh, I won't.
Thanks, Dad.
[ELYMAS] A Fang of
Smoldering Insanity skill book
is essential
for making my class viable.
It'd be great if I were able
to find one
somewhere in this city.
Hmm.
Excuse me.
Could you give me
three healing potions?
Sure thing. It's 72,000 gold.
[ELYMAS] That's a whole lot
more expensive
than it was in the game.
Then again, I guess
there's no way around it.
-[coins jingle]
-Very well.
By the way,
I have a question for you.
Mm?
Do you know where I can buy
some skill books?
Oh.
They don't seem to be available
in any shops around here.
A Heavy Knight is stuck
in tutorial mode
until they find a Fang of
Smoldering Insanity skill book.
I have to get my hands on one.
[CLERK] Really?
You don't know anything, do you?
If I had to guess, I'd say
you're a first-year adventurer
who just got his class, right?
Uh, yeah.
Purchasing and selling
skill books
is strictly prohibited.
Huh?
People who acquire a skill book
are allowed to use it,
of course.
But any extra or unused ones
must be turned over
to the Adventurer's Guild,
where they're sold off
to the church affiliates
and nobles.
[gasps] You're kidding!
They're an incredibly rare drop.
It's assumed
you have to buy them,
and they'll cost a lot of gold.
Though, there's only
a small chance that you'll find
the one you're looking for.
From the beginning,
it did feel like the nobles
out here were more powerful
than they were in the game,
but I can't believe this is
what's actually happening.
At this point,
it wouldn't surprise me
if the skill books in Rondalm
have all been bought up
and hidden away by my family,
the Edvaughns.
[sighs]
-All right, fine.
-Huh?
[CLERK] I'm not supposed
to tell you this,
but I'll make an exception
just this once.
[scribbling]
After all, you bought
the healing potions.
Here. Give that place a try.
What's this?
It's a shop known for dealing
in scavenged goods.
[ELYMAS] Don't scavengers loot
dead adventurers?
I don't understand.
If any of those items are found,
aren't they supposed
to be reported
to the Adventurer's Guild?
[CLERK] Well, they have
an unspoken agreement.
Although the guild knows
about these underground shops,
they usually
just turn a blind eye.
There are plenty of adventurers
who wouldn't survive
without scavenging
every once in a while.
Even if they chose
to follow standard procedure,
most items would just end up
in the hands of nobles
instead of
their surviving families.
[gasps]
[CLERK] Rather than using them,
nobles buy up skill books
for almost nothing,
and then hoard the ones
they've gathered.
They don't know how hard
it is to be an adventurer.
[seething]
[ELYMAS] I'm starting to realize
how utterly naive I was.
If the memories of my past life
had never returned,
and I'd become
a Master Swordsman...
[CLERK] Now, don't go around
telling the mucky-mucks
about this shop, all right?
-[ELYMAS] No, I won't.
-[bell jingles]
I'd rather die
a slow death than tell anyone
that I'm really the son
of a noble.
[sighs]
[birds chirping]
♪
Yeah!
-Nice!
-That was fun, huh?
[laughing]
Come on! You're not gonna
catch me this time!
[birds chirping]
[sighs]
Hmm.
[door creaks]
[coughing]
[♪ ominous music playing]
[ELYMAS] Will I really find
skill books
in a place like this?
Right there. I see five of them.
That's some dinky armor.
[gasps]
The Hall of Broken Grimoires
is a shop for those
who are more experienced,
not for newbies like you.
I, uh, I have some gold.
Mind if I look
at those skill books?
You're more than welcome
to look.
Those filthy fingerprints
of yours aren't going
to make them less valuable.
Thank you.
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Beginner Archery Skill book.
Market price, two million gold.
[Elymas gasps] Unbelievable!
That's 500,000 gold
more than it is in the game!
In Magic World,
the market price
was based on trades
made between all the players.
Then again,
the price for this item
is probably based
on actual trade prices too.
I'll bet the cost of every
skill book here is inflated
due to nobles hoarding them.
Just know if you plan
on buying that,
I'll be charging
three million gold.
What?! Three million?!
Well, naturally.
This is a risky business
I'm running here.
And so far, the officials
have been looking the other way.
But if their superiors learned
of this, I could lose my head.
[Elymas groans] Even these basic
beginner skill books
are expensive.
If I ever decided
to sell the Daemonsrage Shield,
I would only have
three million gold.
Something tells me
I'd need more than that
if I want to buy
a rare skill book.
[inhales]
Hmm.
[ELYMAS] Beginner Archery,
Magic Booster,
Jack-in-the-Box,
and Elemental Guard.
Actually, all four of these
are pretty rare.
But they're still not
what I'm looking for.
What's this last one?
[gasps]
[spluttering]
This is it! [gasps]
The skill tree essential
to Heavy Knights.
Fang of Smoldering Insanity!
Once I have it, I'm golden!
-[SHOPKEEP] What's this?
-[gasps]
You seem happy.
But if that's what you want,
then you must be a weirdo.
Ma'am, how much
would this one be?
Uh-huh!
I'd charge 50 million.
[gasps sharply]
[sighs]
I'm amazed you're displaying
such an expensive item
with no guards here.
[scoffs] If you think
I'm a weakling,
play around and find out.
I've thrown big guys
out on their asses.
[sighs]
Hmm?
I have to have this.
So do you think
you can hold it here for me?
I promise, I'll come back
with 50 million gold.
[Elymas groans]
-[coughs]
-And what's in it for me
if I say yes?
[gasps]
Well, I, uh...
Kid, you do have spirit,
I'll give you that much.
-[ELYMAS] Huh?
-All right. I can hold it.
-You really will?
-Sure.
For an extra
five million gold. Hmm?
[Elymas gasps] This lady drives
a hard bargain.
[laughs]
[ELYMAS]
Guess I'd better find ways
of making money for a while.
[birds chirping]
♪
[indistinct chatter]
[ADVENTURER] Tell me,
how'd it go with them?
We made a perfect team.
-And then, boom!
-No?
[all laughing]
[WOMAN 1] Do you like
how it turned out?
[WOMAN 2] That's really cute!
[sighs]
Fifty-five million gold, huh?
I'd have to earn 60 times
what I made
on that last raid quest.
High-level adventurers
and the shops
they do business with,
really seem to have
a busted perspective of wealth.
Fang of Smoldering Insanity
is one of the rarest
skill trees,
but the only people
with a reason to build it
are other Heavy Knights
and combat junkies
with a major death wish.
The skill books that are
more obviously powerful
must be ridiculously expensive.
[sighs] I have to come up
with a practical way
to earn gold.
I could try getting rich quick
farming rare drops in dungeons.
No. Heavy Knights
don't have the skills
to deal consistent damage.
I could start farming
weak monsters.
[grunting]
No, that would take
way too much time.
I could try to look
for some other skill books
and build up
those skill trees instead.
No. I'd stop using them all
once I acquired
Fang of Smoldering Insanity.
Hmm.
And I'd like to avoid
wasting my skill points.
[sighs]
Can't believe
I was so rude to that guy.
[indistinct chatter, laughter]
[ELYMAS] While I know
Heavy Knights aren't popular,
that raid quest
still should have
gotten my name out there.
I'd have a lot more options
if I teamed up
with other adventurers.
Ah. Allies.
[gasps]
I'll keep it busy
so you can escape.
So don't you worry
about a thing.
-[grunts]
-[Wight snarls]
[both panting]
[Gowtan grunts]
How dare you doubt
Elymas's abilities?!
I am the one
who approved his promotion,
so you're all insulting me
as well!
I guess I'll find allies.
[MAN] Oh, man. I had no idea
Blood-Soaked Sword
was going to drop.
Hmm.
[MAN] The market price for it
is two million gold.
We can have a little fun
with that for a while.
[giggling]
Seems like my skills
really helped us out
quite a bit,
don't ya think?
-[WOMAN] Silence.
-[girl groans]
[GIRL] Aw. Come on, you guys.
I thought they worked
pretty well, didn't they?
[ELYMAS] Pretty sure
that's a swordsman, a bandit,
and a pierrot.
You think you helped?
After visiting the dungeon
a bunch of times,
we finally got this rare drop.
So it was only a matter
of persistence and luck,
not your skills.
Uh... [chuckles awkwardly]
-Yeah, you're right.
-[sighs]
That said, when we visit
some more dungeons together,
I think you'll start seeing
a big difference!
After all,
we're just getting started.
-Don't give me that, Ruche.
-[RUCHE] Huh?
[gasps]
After such a weak performance
like that,
you think you're getting a cut
of the sale?
What?
[chuckles smugly]
[♪ ominous music playing]
But...
Wait. I was risking my life
fighting on the front lines,
just like the rest of you did.
So couldn't I just
get an equal share?
No, hold on.
If I could have 200,000
or even 100,000 gold,
-that would be plenty.
-[MAN] What?
Only kidding.
[sighs]
Listen.
You may be risking
your life out there,
but you don't have
any decent attack skills.
All you do is stand around
-and soak up some hits.
-[gasps]
That's the problem.
Are we clear?
The truth is,
you're not actually useful.
[gasps]
[whimpering]
I...
I don't have any attack skills.
Huh?
[RUCHE] Because after gaining
my skill points,
I spent them
the way you told me to.
-What's that?
-[Ruche gasps]
After we earned something
as a team,
don't you think that it's mean
to say those things to me?
[MAN] Excuse me?
[Ruche whimpering]
[MAN] So, I'm being "mean,"
is that it?
Sounds to me like
you're a little confused.
[gasps]
You see, I just have a problem
giving up a portion
of our take
to somebody who did nothing.
Besides,
I only made a suggestion.
You're the one who assigned
your skill points, remember?
I can't believe you're actually
blaming me
and demanding a share
after showing both of us
how incompetent you are.
[whimpering] Mr. Cline?
[ELYMAS]
She got her build wrong,
and now they're fighting over
how to split the treasure.
Seems like this happened
all the time
in Magic World too.
You assign your skill points
to fit your party,
but the situation changes.
And then your choices
become meaningless.
-Fine, fine.
-[Ruche whimpering]
-[coins jingling]
-[CLINE] Here you go.
[whimpers]
One hundred thousand.
[gasps]
[CLINE] This is what
you wanted, right?
So pick it up
and get out of here.
Even though
your attack skills are weak,
we took pity on you
and still kept you around.
But now you're blinded
by chump change
and showing us your true colors.
-Isn't she?
-Hmm?
[CLINE] Don't you agree, Reiss?
[Reiss sighs]
Yeah. I guess so.
Just 'cause we got
some decent loot,
it's not as if we can afford
to share it with anyone.
Oh, no, you don't understand!
That isn't what I meant!
Uh, please forgive me!
Both of you!
I don't really need any gold
for the sword!
-You can keep it.
-Your apologies won't cut it!
-[whimpering]
-[CLINE] We've had enough.
[gasps]
[♪ somber music playing]
Well, good luck
with your next party, at least.
Then again, if I'm being honest,
I can't imagine
who'd wanna recruit a loser
who can't level up anymore
because of their awful build.
But who knows!
[Ruche sobbing]
[ELYMAS] They say
relationships only last
as long as the money does.
The skill point system
is particularly brutal.
[Ruche sobbing]
[ELYMAS] You have to
farm monsters
that are at or above your level
to get any decent experience.
It's the only way to advance.
Listen,
you may be risking your life,
but you have no attack skills.
All you do is stand there
and soak up hits.
You're not actually useful.
[gasps]
[ELYMAS] But if your build
isn't viable,
and you're constantly struggling
to beat enemies
at your own level...
No!
...raising your level
can become incredibly difficult.
[sobbing]
[ELYMAS] I wonder if she put
her points in Speed Booster
or a weapon skill tree
that she doesn't even need.
As a pierrot,
is it a support tree?
Didn't think
a Blood-Soaked Sword would drop.
Hmm?
[giggling]
Seems like my skills
really helped us out
quite a bit,
don't ya think?
[RUCHE] Aw, come on, you guys!
I thought they worked
pretty well, didn't they?
You think you helped us?
After visiting the dungeon
a bunch of times,
we finally got this rare drop.
So it was only a matter
of persistence and luck,
not your skills.
[Elymas gasps] Could it be?
-[Ruche sobbing]
-Does she have that skill tree?
If he realized it,
then he never would've
kicked her out like that.
But based on what they said,
I'm almost positive
she has a certain
rare skill tree
that's utterly broken
if you know how it works.
[RUCHE] I'm so sorry
for being selfish!
You don't ever
have to pay me again, okay?
I promise! Please say
you'll keep me in the party
-and I'll-- [gasps]
-[Elymas grunts]
-[panting heavily]
-[gasps]
Uh, who are you, mister?
[ELYMAS] Hear me out!
[screams]
-[BOTH] Huh?
-[Ruche screams]
[Elymas panting]
Please! There's nothing
to be scared of.
I just want you
to form a party with me!
A p-party?!
[both gasp]
[panting heavily]
[Ruche whimpers]
[♪ closing theme song playing]
[ELYMAS] After figuring out
I needed to join a team,
I started looking
for party members.
So I reached out
to a pierrot girl.
Ugh, now that I think about it,
maybe that was
a bit sketchy of me.
That said,
the ones who kicked her
out of their group
didn't even realize
what they had.
But I can see how truly valuable
her skills will be.
Next time, "Ruche the Pierrot."
To succeed,
I have to recruit her.